this problem asks
us to capitalize the value of our local
variable state
and then print the modified value
state should have the modified value
both before
and after we print it so looking on line
one
we can see the local variable state and
the value it references
if you're aware of the string capitalize
method
this problem may seem pretty
straightforward
so let's output
the return value of calling the string
capitalize method
on state
and our output matches the expected
output
now the problem description tells us
that state should have the
modified value both before and after
we print its capitalized form
so on line 4 let's output state again
and see if it retained that modification
you can see that it didn't the first
line of output
is the result of us invoking capitalize
on state
we passed the return value of that
method call as an argument to put s
however on the next line of output when
we pass just state to put s
you can see that the original string was
printed and
it hasn't been changed
let's go back and look at our code
so because we want state to have the
modified value
both before and after we print it we
need to use a destructive method
we used a non-destructive capitalize
method
which returned a new string it did not
modify the original string
so in order to get the intended behavior
for this problem
we need to mutate or modify the original
string in place
and we can do that using the destructive
capitalize method
so let's run our code again and see if
we successfully modified the string in
place
and we did now you can see that when we
output
state after our method invocation
it has retained that modified state
and that's because we used a destructive
method and mutated that original value
you